<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>admin &#8211; © Al Mashal Ship Management Services LLC &#8211; All Rights Resereved.</title>
	<atom:link href="/author/almashalsms/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/</link>
	<description></description>
	<lastBuildDate>Wed, 18 Oct 2017 18:45:51 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>hourly</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>1</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=4.8.7</generator>
	<item>
		<title>Our Managed Fleets</title>
		<link>/our-managed-fleets/</link>
		<pubDate>Wed, 18 Oct 2017 11:25:52 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">/?p=63</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[Bulk Trans loaders MV Trans Gulf    ( Trans Loader 72000 DWT ) MV Trans Bay     ( Trans Loader 70000 DWT) MV Trans Emirates ( Trans loader 70000 DWT)   Bulk Carriers MV Pearl Of Jebel Ali  ( Bulk Carrier 65000 DWT) MV Star Of Dubai  ( Bulk Carrier 83600 [&#8230;]]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><strong><u>Bulk Trans loaders</u></strong></p>
<ul>
<li><strong>MV Trans Gulf    ( Trans Loader 72000 DWT )</strong></li>
<li><strong>MV Trans Bay     ( Trans Loader 70000 DWT)</strong></li>
<li><strong>MV Trans Emirates ( Trans loader 70000 DWT)</strong></li>
</ul>
<p><strong> </strong></p>
<p><strong><u>Bulk Carriers</u></strong></p>
<ul>
<li><strong>MV Pearl Of Jebel Ali  ( Bulk Carrier 65000 DWT)</strong></li>
<li><strong>MV Star Of Dubai  ( Bulk Carrier 83600 DWT )</strong></li>
</ul>
<p><strong> </strong></p>
<p><strong><u>Tankers</u></strong></p>
<ul>
<li><strong>MT Abu Dhabi Star (Tanker 51000 DWT)</strong></li>
<li><strong>MT Emirates Star (Tanker 51000 DWT) </strong></li>
</ul>
<p><strong> </strong></p>
<p><strong><u>Containers</u></strong></p>
<ul>
<li><strong>CS Setubal </strong></li>
<li><strong>CS Tina </strong></li>
</ul>
]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Procurement</title>
		<link>/procurement/</link>
		<pubDate>Wed, 18 Oct 2017 09:45:46 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">/?p=51</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[To us, purchasing is more than a process of acquiring supplies. It is procuring the best quality goods and services at the most economical price. Through tapping on our global purchasing experience, and our network of highly reliable suppliers, we actively negotiate for favorable frame agreements and consolidate volume purchase. [&#8230;]]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<h4>To us, purchasing is more than a process of acquiring supplies. It is procuring the best quality goods and services at the most economical price. Through tapping on our global purchasing experience, and our network of highly reliable suppliers, we actively negotiate for favorable frame agreements and consolidate volume purchase. As a result, we are not only able to secure attractive pricing on a range of supplies, including spare parts, lubricating oil, paints and provisions, we are also able to adopt a holistic perspective to inventory control – maximizing savings for our principals. Furthermore, our computerized purchasing system, fully integrated with our AMOS Planned Maintenance System on board vessels, assures that incidents of over-stocking are minimized.</h4>
]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Crew Management</title>
		<link>/crew-management/</link>
		<pubDate>Wed, 18 Oct 2017 09:45:02 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">/?p=49</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[At Al Mashal Ship Management, we recognize the value of deploying seafarers who are well-trained and certified in accordance with STCW 2010 and the ISM Code. Our primary concern is to deliver safe, efficient, high quality, ethical and cost effective ship management solutions that satisfy our customers. The company offers [&#8230;]]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<h4>At Al Mashal Ship Management, we recognize the value of deploying seafarers who are well-trained and certified in accordance with STCW 2010 and the ISM Code. Our primary concern is to deliver safe, efficient, high quality, ethical and cost effective ship management solutions that satisfy our customers.</h4>
<h4></h4>
<h4>The company offers a comprehensive range of crew management services that may be tailored to a client’s requirements. Our company utilizes crewing software specifically developed in-house, which enables us to provide our clients with information on crew planning and crew pooling in line with their requirements.</h4>
<h4>With an experienced work force spread across its network of offices, Al Mashal Ship management is well positioned to meet today’s challenges of crew management.</h4>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Technical Management</title>
		<link>/technical-management/</link>
		<pubDate>Wed, 18 Oct 2017 09:43:13 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">/?p=46</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[Technical Management package includes any or all of the services listed below, structured to meet any client’s individual requirements: Ø Management and maintenance of vessels in compliance with International and National regulations, applicable codes, industry standards and best practices. Ø Implementation of our Quality, Safety and Environmental Management System, providing [&#8230;]]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<h4>Technical Management package includes any or all of the services listed below, structured to meet any client’s individual requirements:</h4>
<h4>Ø Management and maintenance of vessels in compliance with International and National regulations, applicable codes, industry standards and best practices.</h4>
<h4>Ø Implementation of our Quality, Safety and Environmental Management System, providing practical and efficient processes and procedures that allow full and effective implementation on board.</h4>
<h4></h4>
<h4><u> </u></h4>
<h4>Ø Allocation of qualified and experienced management personnel.</h4>
<h4>Ø Dedicated and reliable technical support provided 24/7.</h4>
<h4>Ø Cost-effective, economic and efficient procurement of provisions, stores, consumables and lubricating oils, with access to competitive price agreements and terms with preferred suppliers.</h4>
<h4>Ø Maintenance of the vessel to an agreed high standard including planned and preventive maintenance strategies and cost effective repair program.</h4>
<h4>Ø Dry-dock planning, supervision and post-docking monitoring and follow-up.</h4>
<h4>Ø Class and Flag survey planning and certification.</h4>
<h4>Ø Effect budgeting, cost control, comparison and analysis. Formulation of cost reduction strategies across a client’s technical operations.</h4>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
